0	An error was found in this version of 9Dragons.$;$;We apologize for the inconvenience.$;$;You can help make the game more stable by sending us a report on the related files.$;$;Click Send to send an error report. If you don't wish to send a report, click Cancel.
1	Send ID
2	Sending a report.
3	Failed to connect to the Internet.
4	Could not find the correct file path.
5	Report sent.
6	Cannot read server address.
7	Send
8	Cancel
_XM_EOS
